export const data1 = [

        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 3,
            "question": "Proposed Center Full Address with PIN Code : (Hamara Kendra)",
            "answer": "271, Solitaire Corporate Park, Andheri Ghatkoper Link Road, Chakala Near Satam Wadi, Mumbai, Maharashtra ",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "MultilineTextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 500,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "0",
            "newFeild": "400093",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"

        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 134,
            "question": "Proposed Center Address Document",
            "answer": "password",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "DropDownList",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 0,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "HK Center Document",
            "newFeild": "File Name",
            "isApproved":1,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 2, 
            "question": "Proposed Center Premises",
            "answer": "Rented",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "RadioButtonList",
            "question_ctrl_value": "Owned_Rented",
            "question_ctrl_length": 0,
            "is_mandatory": 0,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": 0,
            "newFeild": "",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 139,
            "question": "POA Document",
            "answer": "PAN Card",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "DropDownList",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 0,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "HK Center Document",
            "newFeild": "File Name",
            "isApproved":1,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 129,
            "question": "Education Qualification & Document",
            "answer": "HSC",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "RadioButtonList",
            "question_ctrl_value": "QUALIFICATION",
            "question_ctrl_length": 0,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": 1,
            "newFeild": "File Name",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },

        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 61,
            "question": "adhaar Centre Full Address with PIN Code",
            "answer": "271, Solitaire Corporate Park, Andheri Ghatkoper Link Road, Chakala Near Satam Wadi, Mumbai, Maharashtra ",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "MultilineTextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 500,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "AadhaarCentreDocuments",
            "newFeild": "400093",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 139,
            "question": "Aadhaar Center Document:",
            "answer": "Aadhar Card",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "DropDownList",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 0,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "HK Center Document",
            "newFeild": "File Name",
            "isApproved":1,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 52,
            "question": "UID Certificate(SIFY/NSEIT) Number",
            "answer": "12345",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "TextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 50,
            "is_mandatory": 0,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "Operator/Supervisor",
            "newFeild":"File Name",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 50,
            "question": "Name of Operator / Supervisor",
            "answer": "Name Name",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "TextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 50,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": 0,
            "newFeild": "",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 51,
            "question": "Operator / Supervisor Aadhaar Number",
            "answer": "",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "TextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 12,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "Operator/Supervisor",
            "newFeild": "File Name",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },

        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 53,
            "question": "Supervisor / Operator Date Of Birth",
            "answer": "05-06-2013",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "DateTextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "WaterMark_DD/MM/YYYY",
            "question_ctrl_length": 10,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": 1,
            "newFeild": "",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 54,
            "question": "Verifier Name & Document",
            "answer": "Name Name",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "TextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 50,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "POI",
            "newFeild": "File Name",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 55,
            "question": "Verifier Full Address with PIN Code",
            "answer": "271, Solitaire Corporate Park, Andheri Ghatkoper Link Road, Chakala Near Satam Wadi, Mumbai, Maharashtra ",
            // "answer": null,
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "MultilineTextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 500,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "POA",
            "newFeild": "400093",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 57,
            "question": "Verifier Date of Birth",
            "answer": "04-06-2024",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "DateTextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "WaterMark_DD/MM/YYYY",
            "question_ctrl_length": 10,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": 0,
            "newFeild": "",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 56,
            "question": "Verifier Mobile No",
            "answer": "8867565454",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "TextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 10,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": 0,
            "newFeild": "",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },

        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 58,
            "question": "Job/Department",
            "answer": "JOB",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "TextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 100,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": 0,
            "newFeild": "",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"Job Dont match"
        },
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 59,
            "question": "Designation/Post of Verifier",
            "answer": "Designation",
            // "answer":null,
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "TextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "",
            "question_ctrl_length": 100,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": "Pensioner Details",
            "newFeild": "File Name",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        },      
        {
            "enquiry_id": 185620,
            "question_id": 60,
            "question": "Date of Retirment",
            "answer": "02-06-2024",
            "enquiry_type": "VLE",
            "question_ctrl_type": "DateTextBox",
            "question_ctrl_value": "WaterMark_DD/MM/YYYY",
            "question_ctrl_length": 10,
            "is_mandatory": 1,
            "Do_It_Later": null,
            "is_document": 0,
            "newFeild": "",
            "isApproved":0,
            "ccRemark":"you doc is blurred"
        }
    ];
